virginia.org 2010-06-23

# Privacy - Statewide - Virginia Is For Lovers

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, contact Dave Neudeck, Electronic Marketing Director by phone at (804) 545-5554 or email [dneudeck@virginia.org.](mailto:dneudeck@virginia.org)

**Information Collection and Use**

Virginia Tourism Corporation (VTC) collects information from our users at several different points on our website. If you choose to offer us your e-mail address, name, address, phone or comments, we store this information in a tourism database and it is available to tourism facilities. Information about contests, surveys, special offers and savings and newsletters may be sent to you from VTC and Virginia tourism partners. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our opt-out below. 

Addresses collected to send a physical postcard are not shared or sold, but used for the sole purpose of postcard fulfillment. Email addresses are stored to communicate the retrieval of postcards with senders and recipients. Opting-in to receive a Virginia Travel Guide or receive Virginia eNewsletters allows Virginia Tourism Corporation to store information in a database to manage fulfillment of said products. 

**Order**

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address). This information is used to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take may place or use the Trip Planner feature. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Content and Information Disclaimer**

Content and information contained in this site has been compiled by the Virginia Tourism Corporation, based on data submitted directly from local tourism promotion agencies and business entities. While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of this information, all data is subject to change without notice. Travelers are advised to contact individual businesses or organizations to obtain information to their satisfaction before traveling. VTC does not endorse or recommend any specific facility or organization contained in this site. 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that VTC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). Other information requested may include contact information (shipping address and phone number), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. We will also share contact information with companies who partner with VTC for the contests. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Rules for[Jamestown1607.org](http://www.jamestown1607.org/ "http://www.jamestown1607.org/") Website Comment Posting**

Content – Comments should focus on the personalities, locations, stories and opinions surrounding the history, heritage, themes and topics of this website, which include: Jamestown1607 – The most intriguing story in American History and America’s 400th Anniversary: Jamestown 2007. Try to keep comments concise. Comments must not be obscene, profane, sexually explicit, libelous, slanderous, defamatory, harmful, threatening, illegal or knowingly false. Please use the proper grammar to express yourself. No website links or advertisements can be posted. Disclaimer – The Virginia Tourism Corporation (VTC) is not liable for the opinions or validity of any outside sources cited of comments posted. VTC has authority to post or remove comments at its discretion. Comments will be posted on the website with only the name you enter, without the eMail address. Your name and eMail address are still required when initially leaving your comment, so that we can contact you. Your eMail address will not be sold to a third party for marketing purposes. By posting to this forum, you assume responsibility for your communications and the consequences of posting them. Therefore, there will be a delay period between submission and display of accepted items on the Web site. For More Information – Please [sign up for Virginia’s eNewsletter](http://www.virginia.org/site/brochure.asp?nwsltr=1 "http://www.virginia.org/site/brochure.asp?nwsltr=1") or [2007 Travel Guide](http://www.virginia.org/site/main.asp?referrer=publications "http://www.virginia.org/site/main.asp?referrer=publications") to receive updates about [America’s 400th Anniversary](http://www.jamestown1607.org/ "http://www.jamestown1607.org/"), and [visiting Virginia all year-round](http://www.virginia.org/ "http://www.virginia.org/"). 

**Special Offers**

VTC will occasionally send information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter to email addresses collected on the site. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our opt-out below.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. 

**Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [webmaster@virginia.org](mailto:webmaster@virginia.org)

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
